BEAU HUNTER

 $hunter 0907@gmail.com \cdot 801\text{-}557\text{-}4196 \cdot Riverton \ , \ Utah\\ \textbf{linkedin.com/in/beau-hunter-592bab170/ \cdot github.com/BeauSef \cdot }$

Currently has his sights set on a new career as a full-stack developer. 10+ years of customer service experience in a law enforcement and a retail environment. Skilled in, Cashiering, Microsoft word, customer service, and many more. Works well in a team type environment or alone, and a problem solver with many great ideas. Has experience with Git terminal, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, API's Firebase, and Ajax. Currently enrolled in the coding boot camp through the University of Utah which will end in April of 2019 with my certification of a full-stack developer.

EXPERIENCE

JANUARY 2015 - PRESENT

DEPUTY FOR CORRECTIONS & PUBLIC SAFETY BUREAU, SALT LAKE COUNTY SHERIFF'S OFFICE

- Monitor cameras, review footage of incidents, and upload to files. Monitor the public in the courtrooms and in the area to ensure they do not have contraband, weapons, through the screening process with the magnetometer and x-ray machine.
- Help with the hiring process which included interviews of eligible candidate, interviewing neighbors about candidate, checking criminal and credit score rating, and make sure the candidate is qualified for a position with the Sheriff's Office.
- Interactions with the public with both positive and negative situations, Responding to
 emergency situations, Report Writing, Perform protection for county council, elected
 officials, judges, and other employees. Maintain security and order in the courtroom,
 direct court operations, test courtroom alarm system to ensure functionality

JUNE 2017 – NOVEMBER 2018 FIRST TIME MAY 2012 – MAY 2015 CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE, BIG LOTS

- Cashiering with many forms of payment while making sure it's not fraudulent, returning unwanted items, and answer phones to make sure customers are satisfied.
- Assist customers with signing up for financial leasing and credit cards.
- Assist customers in all departments of the store, read planogram to set up displays, and make sure store inventory is stocked to help boost sells.

OCTOBER 2011 – JULY 2016 DEPARTMENT SUPERVISOR, THE HOME DEPOT

- Order product for building and lumber department to keep in stock to higher sales which was one of the highest growths in the district.
- Disciplinary Action for employees and figuring out if it was a training issue and provide feedback to help them. Performance reviews to make sure employees understand what's expected of them. Make sure they are noticed for what they excel in and make sure they understand what they can do better so there is always room for improvement.

- Deal with unsatisfied customers to make sure all theirs needs were met by the best intentions possible.
- Making sure staffing and shifts were covered, allow for times people may call in sick and adapt to those changes to make sure everything runs smoothly.

JUNE 2010 – APRIL 2012
CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE, JCPENNEY

APRIL 2008 – JUNE 2010 CUSTODIAN, FOOTHILLS ELEMANTRY

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2018 APRIL 2019

FULL-STACK DEVELOPING BOOT CAMP, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

- An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications.
- Skills learned HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase.

AUGUST 2014 – MAY 2015
GENERALS, SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, API's, JSON, AJAX, Firebase, GIT, GitHub
- Cashiering, Customer Service, POS Systems